const HtmlA = [
    {
        id: "1",
        Question: "1.What does HTML stand for ?",
        Answer: "Hypertext Markup Language",
    },
    {
        id: "2",
        Question: "2.What is the purpose of HTML?",
        Answer: "HTML is used to create structured documents that are displayed on the web.",
    },
    {
        id: "3",
        Question: "3.What is a tag in HTML?",
        Answer: "A tag is a code that is used to define HTML elements within a document.",
    },
    {
        id: "4",
        Question: "4.What is the difference between HTML and CSS?",
        Answer: "HTML is used to create the structure and content of a web page, while CSS is used to define the appearance and style of the web page",
    },
    {
        id: "5",
        Question: "5.What is the syntax for creating an HTML tag?",
        Answer: "Tags are enclosed within angle brackets (< >) and consist of a tag name, which defines the type of element, and attributes, which provide additional information about the element",
    },
    {
        id: "6",
        Question: "6.What is the difference between an HTML element and an HTML attribute?",
        Answer: "An HTML element is a basic building block of an HTML document that defines the structure and content of a web page, while an HTML attribute is used to provide additional information about an element"
    },
    {
        id: "7",
        Question: "7.What is the role of a doctype declaration in an HTML document?",
        Answer: "The doctype declaration tells the web browser which version of HTML is being used and ensures that the web page is displayed correctly"
    },
    {
        id: "8",
        Question: "8.What is the difference between an ordered list and an unordered list in HTML?",
        Answer: "An ordered list displays items in a numbered list, while an unordered list displays items in a bulleted list.",
    },
    {
        id: "9",
        Question: "9.What is the purpose of the alt attribute in an image tag?",
        Answer: "The alt attribute is used to provide alternative text for an image, which is displayed if the image cannot be loaded or if the user is using a screen reader",
    },
    {
        id: "10",
        Question: "10.What is the difference between a div tag and a span tag in HTML?",
        Answer: "A div tag is used to create a block-level element, while a span tag is used to create an inline element.",
    },
    {
        id: "11",
        Question: "11.What is the purpose of the title tag in HTML?",
        Answer: "The title tag is used to define the title of a web page, which is displayed in the browser tab",
    },
    {
        id: "12",
        Question: "12.What is the purpose of the href attribute in an anchor tag?",
        Answer: "The href attribute is used to define the URL of the web page or file that the link points to.",
    },
    {
        id: "13",
        Question: "13.What is the purpose of the target attribute in an anchor tag?",
        Answer: "The target attribute is used to define where the linked web page or file should be opened, such as in a new window or tab"
    },
    {
        id: "14",
        Question: "14.What is the purpose of the form tag in HTML?",
        Answer: "The form tag is used to create a form that allows users to enter and submit data.",
    },
    {
        id: "15",
        Question: "15.What is the difference between a GET request and a POST request in an HTML form?",
        Answer: " A GET request submits form data as part of the URL, while a POST request submits form data in the request body."
    },
    {
        id: "16",
        Question: "16.What is the purpose of the select tag in HTML?",
        Answer: "The select tag is used to create a drop-down list that allows users to select one or more options.",
    },
    {
        id: "17",
        Question: "17.What is the purpose of the option tag in HTML?",
        Answer: "The option tag is used to define an option in a drop-down list created with the select tag.",
    },
    {
        id: "18",
        Question: "18.What is the purpose of the textarea tag in HTML?",
        Answer: "The textarea tag is used to create a text input field that allows users to enter multiple lines of text.",
    },
    {
        id: "19",
        Question: "19.What is the purpose of the table tag in HTML?",
        Answer: "The table tag is used to create a table that displays data in rows and columns.",

    }
]

export default HtmlA;